There are several ways of using Artview.
By just typing 'artview' you start the default.
See the options with -h.
For instance, -F open a file directly.
Use arrow keys to move between files:
Right open the next file in the folder,
Left the previous.
ARTview use Py-ART to open files.
It opens PPI files,
RHI files,
and Airborne files.
You may also open with Py-ART,
and use ARTview in the Python terminal.
Use 'artview.view.view' for that.
Use arrow keys to changes sweeps:
Down for previous sweep,
Up for the next.
Also use drop-down menus to change
sweep and field,
or open radio menus.
You may change the colorbar limits,
and the axes limits.
Change title,
the units,
and the colormap
Select the zoom tool,
Zoom in and out with the mouse wheel,
pan with the left button.
Use the 'Click for Value' tool to acess the data.
Save the plot to a image file.
Artview is really versatil,
you may open multiple displays
to compare your data
You may also link displays:
the fields are unlinked:
the displays show diferent fields
the fields are linked:
the displays share the same field,
changing one, changes the other.
ARTview has plug-ins for some
of the Py-ART functions
For instance, Mapper uses 'pyart.map.grid_from_radars'
ARTview also work with grided data,
and uses 'pyart.io.write_grid' to save
the grid to a file
ARTview has also original features,
like selecting a subset of the data.
View the data in a table,
save in a file,
and get statatic informations.
You may also write your own
program in ARTview.
For instance: just one display, no menu.